# MUHAMMED KHALED

Proactive and creative professional with high technical skills and eight years track record of delivering excellent customer service and achieving a variety of targets.

## **CONTACT ME HERE:**

Mobile: +447717817341 Email: it.hashedi@gmail.com Address: Colindale, London

Portfolio: www.muhammedkhaled.com

# **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

Proactive and creative professional, with a huge passion for Information Technology. Recently achieved a Second-Class degree in Computer Science in summer 2021. During my studies, I have been freelancing and working with several high-end brands such as Printwell, Utility Warehouse, Greensleeves Lawn Care, and more. Within this time, I have amassed a wealth of experience and skills across Technical Support, Software Development, UI/UX design, Customer Service, Business Operations, Leadership, and Management.

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor Degree in Computer Science . LTU - 2021
HND in Computing . CCL - 2020
HNC in Computing. Nescot- 2019
Foundation in Business and Computing . LBIC - 2018

# **CORE SKILLS**

#### CERTIFICATIONS

Google IT Support Professional Certification - Google
TOTAL: CompTIA A+ Certification (220-1001) - Udemy
The Complete Web Development - Zero To Mastery Academy
Responsive Web Design Certification - Free Code Camp
Modern React.JS - React-Tutorial-App
UI/UX Design - Interaction Design Foundation

- Multilingual (English Arabic and Spanish) Technical Knowledge Problem Solving High Attention to Details Project Management
- Capable of Achieving Targets Ability to Follow Instructions Unique Customer Service & Customer Engagement Project Management

# **TECHNICAL SUPPORT**

Hardware and Software: Mobile phones, tablets, desktops and laptops for macOS, Windows, Linux, IOS and Android operating systems.

Applications: Office 365 suite, G Suite, Citrix, Windows Server, Linux Server, Active Directory, IBM Products, CRMs including Salesforce and Zendesk and Microsoft Intune.

Networking: TCP/IP, DNS, DHCP, VPN, LAN, WAN, Switch management, SCCM, and Remote Connection Support with (RDP+SSH).

Cloud Technologies: Azure, AWS and Google Cloud

Maintenance: Maintaining backups, printers management, installing and upgrading operating systems, software and hardware.

#### **SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT**

Front-End:

HTML, CSS, Bulma, JavaScript, ReactJS, Vue.js, jQuery, Three.js, P5.js and Bootstrap.

Backend:

Python (Flask), Machine Learning, MySQL, NodeJS, Python and PHP.

CMS:

WordPress and Catfish.

Tools:

git, GitLab, Github, npm, yarn, Adobe XD, Photoshop, and Canva.

#### **UI/UX DESIGN**

- Research User Personas Storyboards Customer maps
- Brainstorming User Flows Site maps Low-fidelity prototype
- hand-drawn sketches High-fidelity prototypes interactive prototypes
- Usability Reports Analytics Reports

#### LATEST WORK EXPERIENCE

# Software Developer - Technical Support

Printwell (UK) LTD . Freelance

Mar 2020 - Present . 1 yr

In charge of the full process of the design, development research, and system switch of all Printwell Digital stores along with their products and product redesign and technical support:

- Software Development: designing and developing Printwell's all closed and open online stores
- UI Design: wireframes, high-fidelity prototypes, and testing.
- Product Design: designing all Printwell's Web to Print products using JavaScript and PS.
- Technical Support: communicating with users and solving their issues through emails and phone calls.

#### IT Consultant

Zinrack . Freelance

Feb 2017- Present . 4 yr 1 mo

While freelancing with Zinrack part-time, I offer many services and worked with various brands. My role is very diverse, some of the responsibilities I have are the following:

- Designing, developing and leading small and big projects including front-end and back-end.
- Conducting UX research including user personas, user journeys, and site maps.
- Designing high and low fidelity prototypes along with wireframes.
- Graphic designing of various artworks such as logos, banners, and other marketing materials.
- Communicating with clients and solving their issues through emails and phone calls.
- Designing and maintaining WordPress and Catfish websites (E-commerce and others).

#### OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

# Customer Service & Compliance Officer

Synergy Prime LTD . Employed . Call Centre

Feb 2019 - Jan 2020. 1 yr

Managing a team of 12 agents and ensuring that they all meet their KPI targets in terms of customer service, sales, and compliance:

- Monitoring, scoring and documenting agents' calls.
- Giving Feedback to agents in terms of customer service and sales.
- Ensure agents to remain compliant with the regulating bodies such as the FCA.
- Answering customers escalated calls and solving complex issues.
- Preforming a variety of data entry tasks.
- Processing information and writing and filling weekly and daily reports.

#### Sales Rep

London City Tour . Employed . Call Centre Mar 2018 - Jan 2020. 1 yr

# **Project Manager**

Tadom Hill Resorts . Employed . Malaysia sep 2016 - Mar 2017 . 7 mo

#### Receptionist

Menu Lodge . Employed . Malaysia Feb 2015 - Jan 2016 . 11 mo

#### Team Member

Krispy Kreme . Employed Sep 2017- Jun 2018 . 9 mo

# **Personal Assistant**

Bamboo Village . Employed . Malaysia Jan 2016 - Aug 2016 . 6 mo